GRAHAM HARRIS

CONTACT

929.244.0668 grahamh1019@gmail.com Brooklyn, NY

EDUCATION

New York University,
Sept. 2018 – May 2022
GPA: 3.6
Major in Computer
Science
Minors in Mathematics
and Italian

LINKS

GitHub

LinkedIn

Resume Website

SKILLS

- Scrum/Agile
- Project Management
- Data Analysis
- Data Visualization
- Python
- Low/No Code Platforms
- APIs
- Natural Language
 Processing (NLP)
- Large Language
 Models (such as Chat-GPT)

SUMMARY

Technical project manager seeks new role in management or communications. Open to a wide range of positions, including (but not limited to) technical and non-technical management, finance, venture capital, and business/data analysis. Some previous experience in project management, tech development, and seed-stage ventures.

EXPERIENCE

Cloud & Custom Applications Consultant - Capgemini US

June 2022 - Present

Integrations Business Analyst:

- Evaluated 6 cloud solutions for client's business transformation needs.
- Conducted in-depth analysis of business bottlenecks and legacy software tools across 2 engagements.

Data Analyst:

- Documented client's software requirements across 200+ applications for cloud migration.
- Cleaned and structured data for use in 3 of Capgemini's internal data analysis tools.

Scrum Master (Project Manager):

- Facilitated Scrum practices for 2 of client's machine learning team, overseeing a total of 20 developers.
- Achieved 110% velocity measured by Microsoft Azure Dashboards and Queries.

Data Analyst Intern – NYU Entrepreneurial Institute

Sept. 2019 - May 2022

- Analyzed 5 years of aggregate data across 50+ Institute events by creating a behavioral network.
- Organized entrepreneurship events, such as start-up incubators and venture capital pitch-fests.
- Delivered weekly 1-hour long presentations on startup resources at NYU.

PROJECTS

Network Analysis (GitHub Link)

 Created 6 behavioral networks from event data for NYU's Entrepreneurial Institute.

Movie Review Sentiment Analysis (GitHub Link)

 Calculated binary classification and logistic regression to determine sentiment for 50,000 IMDb movie reviews.